Rafael Asmoucha

An eager fast learner looking to develop new skills and build on existing ones. Higly detail orientated with an ambitious personality. Israel, Herzliya

054-5998589

rasmoucha@gmail.com

<u>LinkedIn</u> in

https://Rafis.work



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming in Python, C, JavaScript, HTML and CSS.

MILITARY EXPERIENCE

IDF, Paratroopers Brigade, Battalion 890 - Combat Soldier

NOV 2021 - PRESENT

As a lone soldier, I faced the challenge of integrating into the army as well as Israeli culture, while learning Hebrew. I served in the newly founded "SUFA" team in Tzanhanim. The team's uniquely small size requires more responsibility from each person who must learn to specialise in the operational planning of firepower, communicating directly with the air force and artillery support.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Replit Ventures, Startup Incubator Program - Startup Mail App APR 2021 - JUL 2021

AFR 2021 - JUL 2021

Working in collaboration with a friend, we built an email service app with the aim of innovating in email technology. I had the idea to display email read receipts and designed a modern user-interface.

Our startup was one of six selected from over 400 applicants to participate in Replit Ventures. The incubator program provided me with excellent technical and business mentorship over the course of two months. Additionally, I was invited to weekly workshops with guest speakers from successful startup companies and given access to network within an exclusive community of founders with bright ideas.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

CPU Simulator - Interactive Educational Website

JUL 2021

I created a website which is based on the "Little Man Computer" system that models the architecture of a simple computer with basic instructions. In addition to this, I developed an assembly code editor that acts similarly to a modern IDE, with syntax highlighting. The program compiles any user-inputted assembly code and displays it on the model of a CPU, moving "blobs" to illustrate the computer's operation. https://lmc.rafis.work/

EDUCATION

JFS School, London

2019 - 2021



A-level Computer Science, Mathematics and Media studies.

edX

MOOC (Massive Open Online Courses) Certifications
CS50x: Computer Science (by Harvard University)

2023

Calc001x: Calculus (by TU Delft)